nursingaccelerate.com 2013-06-05

# Nursing Accelerate

## Company Practices Regarding Your Privacy

We at Nursing Accelerate, Inc. and our affiliated companies worldwide are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any information you share with us by using our web sites. Nursing Accelerate has established the following Online Privacy Policy so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your information. This policy describes the overall privacy practices of Nursing Accelerate regarding information we collect on our network of web sites and through our other Internet advertising mediums, including but not limited to email, newsletters, and leave-behinds. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Nursing Accelerate does not own or control, or to people that Nursing Accelerate does not employ.

## Information Collected by Nursing Accelerate

_**Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information**_

Nursing Accelerate collects various types of information from you to better meet your needs and to provide you with a more relevant user experience. Some of this information is collected automatically through cookies (a small text file placed on your computer) or other Internet tracking technologies. The type of information your browser or Internet session may automatically provide us with can include the browser you are using, your Internet domain, the operating system on your computer, your IP address and the URL you saw just before coming to the Nursing Accelerate site, the pages of the site you visited and the URL of the page you visited upon leaving the site. Nursing Accelerate may also contract with reputable third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may also use cookies or other measures to collect your non-personally identifiable information.

## Personally Identifiable Consumer Information

In addition, at some of the Nursing Accelerate web sites, we collect information that you may choose to provide to us when requesting additional information from us or from one or more of our clients. Examples of personally identifiable data that you may provide to us include name, address, and email address. If you provide personally identifiable data to us, you may later elect to have your information deleted from our files, or kept from being used for purposes other than for the service requested, by following the opt-out procedures set forth below.

## How Collected Information is Used

The non-personally identifiable information that Nursing Accelerate collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience. The information is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different individuals. If you elect to provide Nursing Accelerate with personally identifiable information, we may utilize such information for marketing purposes, and this use may result in follow-up communications from Nursing Accelerate and from our clients. In addition, that information may be combined with information collected from other sources to assist with targeting ads to your preferences and behaviors, and for other Nursing Accelerate sales and marketing efforts.

## Sharing Information with Third Parties

All personally identifiable information you provide is maintained in confidence by Nursing Accelerate. There are instances, however, in which your personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information is shared with third parties, as described below. Your non-personally identifiable data may be shared with third-party partners of Nursing Accelerate on an anonymous basis. When you request information from Nursing Accelerate or one or more of our clients, we may transfer that information within Nursing Accelerate or route your information to our client(s), across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world, so that they may provide the information on their product or service that you requested. We may also disclose information to a third party who provides substantially similar services as the original service about which you requested more information. In such situations, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of such sharing. Please be aware that Nursing Accelerate is very careful in selecting companies with whom it does business. In addition to the above situations where your information may be shared with others, there is also the possibility that Nursing Accelerate, or part(s) of the company, may one day be purchased by, or merged with, another company. In the event of such transaction, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to all collected personally identifiable information. Finally, Nursing Accelerate may share your information as necessary to comply with a court order or to cooperate with government and law enforcement officials.

## Security

Wherever your personally identifiable information may be held within Nursing Accelerate or on its behalf, we intend to take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the information you shared with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. Please note that while Nursing Accelerate will make every reasonable effort to protect your information, no transmission of data over the Internet is 100% secure. Choice

**_Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information - Use of Cookies & Opting-Out_**

Some of our web sites utilize cookies to collect information about your website activities and to recall the personal information you previously shared with us. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Blocking cookies may result in a lower quality experience for you while you are visiting Nursing Accelerate web sites.

**_Personally Identifiable Consumer Information - Opting-Out_**

You may choose whether or not to provide personally identifiable information to Nursing Accelerate. If you choose to provide such information to Nursing Accelerate, you have the right to tell us not to make some of the uses of such information described herein or may have such information deleted in its entirety. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, surveys or promotional communications via email, you may opt-out by clicking here and following the instructions to unsubscribe. To have your personal information completely removed from our databases, simply contact us at info@nursingaccelerate.com and provide the name of the service for which information was provided, your full name, mailing address, phone number and email address so that we may identify you in the opt-out process. Once we receive your instruction, we will promptly take corrective action.

## Access/Accuracy

To the extent that you do provide us with personally identifiable information, Nursing Accelerate wishes to maintain the accuracy of this information. Where we collect personally identifiable information from you on the Web, our goal is to provide a means of contacting Nursing Accelerate should you need to update or correct that information. If for any reason those means are unavailable or inaccessible, you may send updates and corrections about your personally identifiable information to info@nursingaccelerate.com and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in the information that we hold as soon as practicable.

## Children's Privacy

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), Nursing Accelerate.com is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect personally identifiable information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.

## Refer a Friend

Some of Nursing Accelerate's web sites offer you the opportunity to easily notify a friend of the offer or information promoted on the site. If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about a Nursing Accelerate site, we will ask you for your friend's personally identifiable information, including name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Nursing Accelerate stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at info@nursingaccelerate.com to request that we remove this information from our database. Our one-time email to your friend will inform him or her of this fact.

## Commitment

Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and Nursing Accelerate's web sites are constantly changing to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Online Privacy Policy, please contact us at info@nursingaccelerate.com. While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as practicable after you bring it to our attention.

## Your Consent

By using this web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to Nursing Accelerate's processing of personally identifiable information for the purposes given above. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time and by amending this privacy policy.
